(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
忘れじの言の葉
Wasureji no Kotonoha
Lyrics: 砂守岳央(未来古代楽団)
Music: 松岡美弥子(未来古代楽団)
Lyrics: Takeo Sunamori (Mirai Kodai Gakudan)
Music: Miyako Matsuoka (Mirai Kodai Gakudan)
忘れじの言の葉を紡いで
Spinning words never to be forgotten
まどろんだ唄方
An ephemeral, drowsy song
旅路に迷い込む
Getting lost on the journey
おとぎの深い霧
In the deep mist of a fairy tale
差しのべた掌
The hand that was reached out
そっと触れる予感
A premonition of a gentle touch
受け止めて零れた
Caught and spilled over
光の一雫
A single drop of light
ロロゼ ヴズィオ ツェラ ジ ジロ リリオ
Loroze vuzio tsera zi ziro ririo
トゥラロ ジ ジロ ジ リリ オ
Turaro zi ziro zi riri o
面影を募って
Longing for a memory
微笑んだ幻
An illusion that smiled
想いの果てる場所
The place where feelings end
まだ遥か遠くて
Is still far, far away
求め探し彷徨って
Seeking and searching, wandering
やがて詠われて
Eventually being sung
幾千幾万幾億の
Thousands, tens of thousands, hundreds of millions
旋律となれ
Become a melody
いつか失い奪われて
Even if one day it is lost and taken away
消える定めでも
And destined to vanish
それは忘れられることなき
It is a never-to-be-forgotten
物語
Story
忘れじの言の葉
The Unforgettable Words
言の葉を紡いで
Weaving words together
まどろんだうたかた
Bubbles in a slumber
旅人の名前を
A traveler's name
おとぎ話という
Called a fairy tale
望み探して彷徨うて　やがて道となり
Wandering in search of hope, it eventually becomes a path
幾千幾万幾億の　悠は往く
Thousands, tens of thousands, millions of eternities pass by
いつか失い奪われて　消える定めでも
Even if it's destined to be lost, taken away, and disappear
それは忘れられることなく　ここにある
It remains here without being forgotten
望み探して彷徨うて　やがて詠われて
Wandering in search of hope, it eventually becomes a song
幾千幾万幾億の　旋律となる
Becoming a melody of thousands, millions, and billions
いつか失い奪われて　消える定めでも
Even if it's destined to be lost, taken away, and disappear
それは忘れられることなき　物語
It's a story that will never be forgotten
モエチャッカファイア
Moe Chakka Fire
さくさく進ませた　ご主人様
You made progress quickly, Master
隣に座って　せーの、萌え萌え萌え
Sit next to me and say, "Ready, moe moe moe!"
こんなんで誰が喜ぶの？
Who's going to be happy with this?
さあ教えて　笑顔でアップップ
Now tell me, with a smile, hold your breath!
挨拶を忘れて　ご苦労様
You forgot your greetings, good work
私が踊るぜ　せーの、パッパッパ
I'm dancing, here we go, pa-pa-pa!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶの？
Who's going to be happy with this?
さあ教えて　笑顔でアップップ
Now tell me, with a smile, hold your breath!
ひらりはらり　女の子
Fluttering, a girl
ふわりふわり　言の葉の園
Softly, in the garden of words
それでつまり　幼女な子
So in short, a little girl
感情的リアル　笑顔でアップップ
Emotional reality, with a smile, hold your breath!
人は見かけによらぬもの
You can't judge a person by their appearance
嘘を嘘と見抜けない
Can't tell a lie from the truth
したたかな袖　裾の皮
Tough sleeves, the skin of the hem
鳥肌覚めら　アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Goosebumps waking up, un, deux, trois
欲しかったご指名　いただきます
I'll take that nomination I wanted
私が踊るぜ　せーの、パッパッパ
I'm dancing, here we go, pa-pa-pa!
これはド派手に　ご苦労様
This is quite flashy, good work
遊びましょう　笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, with a smile, hold your breath!
ひらりはらり　ここはどこ
Fluttering, where is this?
ふわりふわり　さあ let me show
Softly, now let me show
それでつまり　幼女な子
So in short, a little girl
感情的リアル　笑顔でアップップ
Emotional reality, with a smile, hold your breath!
移ろい出す　夢の鐘
The bells of dreams start to fade
終わることのない　この世界
This never-ending world
正しい子も居る
There are good kids too
空しい子も居る
There are empty kids too
眠らせて
Let me sleep
おままごと　遊びましょう　笑顔でアップップ
Let's play house, let's play, with a smile, hold your breath!
ひらりはらり　女の子
Fluttering, a girl
ふわりふわり　言の葉の園
Softly, in the garden of words
それでつまり　幼女な子
So in short, a little girl
感情的リアル　笑顔でアップップ
Emotional reality, with a smile, hold your breath!
遊びましょう　笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, with a smile, hold your breath!
アップップ
Hold your breath!
Hi! Oh my god, hello everyone!
It's the ancient weapon from Hololive ID second generation,
Anya Melfissa!
Hello! Thank you so much for coming
to my 3D birthday live!
Oh my god, finally, finally, finally! Ha!
今日はね、アーニャの誕生日ということで...
Today, as it's Anya's birthday...
...3D!
めっちゃ楽しいです！
I'm having so much fun!
やったー！
Yay!
ねー、見に来てくれてありがとう、みんな！
Hey, thank you all for coming to watch!
Oh my God, I'm so excited.
I'm so, so excited.
Especially since it's my first 3D birthday live.
Yes!
I am so excited.
And I've still got a few more songs
...to sing to you guys.
But first of all, remember to post a lot
...with this hashtag,
#CuriousTune3D.
Remember to post a lot of screenshots...
...and a lot of your, you know, favorite moments.
このハッシュタグでね、ぜひみんな...
Please everyone, with this hashtag...
...いっぱいポストして。あとで見ろから。
...post a lot. I'll check them later.
I'll be checking them out after the live.
Please, please! Yeah.
I think I like the title
...of the 3D birthday live a lot.
I think it's pretty unique.
Through the Curious Tune.
Yeah, I really like that title.
Sounds pretty unique.
Sounds very Anya-like.
And it sure fits this stage.
Look at this!
Look at this stage!
The 3D birthday live stage,
...isn't it so cool and cute?
It's very cool and cute, oh my God.
ねー、このステージ、めっちゃ凄くない？
Hey, isn't this stage really amazing?
ここでね、あの、いっぱい歌うの。
I'm going to sing a lot here.
これからいっぱい歌うんだけど、マジで楽しみ。
I'm singing a lot from now on, I can't wait.
I can't wait to sing a few more songs
...in this stage after this.
And then, at the end...
Oh my God, at the end,
I'll be singing my new original song!
So be sure to watch until the end.
ねー、今日はね、最後で、なんと、オリ曲？
Hey, today, at the end, maybe... an original song?
新しいオリ曲、聴けるかもしれないので、
You might be able to hear a new original song, so...
みんなね、最後まで見てね。
Everyone, please watch until the end.
ということで、ここからも...
And so, from here on...
...まだまだ行きますよ。
...we're still going.
まだまだ歌っていきますよ。
I'm going to keep singing.
ゲストさんたちとね！
With the guests!
I'll be singing with some guests.
Some very, very special guests.
So I hope you guys are as excited as I am!
Yippee!
So, should we go to the next song?
Should we go to the next song? Oh my God.
What is it going to be? What's the next song?
次の曲は、なんだろうな。
What's the next song, I wonder.
行きますかね？次の曲は...
Shall we go? The next song is...
じゃあね、行きましょう！
Alright then, let's go!
次の曲は...
The next song is...
Ai-pau Dancehall!
Yippee! Let's go!
愛包ダンスホール 今日はボレロ とろけ出そうね
Ai-pau Dancehall, today's a bolero, let's melt
甘いスパイ レモン 期待したいね いっぱい満杯
Sweet spy lemon, I want to expect it, full to the brim
お布施のスターは 盛り盛りよ お代わりは
The offering's star is piled high, a refill is...
アンコール次第ね 終わらない ラブコール ムーンダンス
...up to the encore, endless love call moon dance
愛包ダンスホール
Lyrics: Gohgo Music: 凛本シンジ, Gohgo
Ai-pau Dancehall
Lyrics: Gohgo Music: Shinji Rimoto, Gohgo
愛包ダンスホール
Ai-pau Dancehall
お代わりなら もし
If it's for a refill, maybe
愛包ダンスホール
Ai-pau Dancehall
3.14159265のパイだって
Even if it's the 3.14159265 pi
割り切れない気持ち 抱えてるよ
I'm holding onto feelings that don't divide out
ラブ勢も ガチ勢も エンジンも 演者も 円陣組んで...
Love fans, hardcore fans, engines, performers...
...仲良くやれたらとか
...forming a circle and getting along
割り切れない命 さかいのヘヴン
Indivisible life, the heaven of the border
今夜はいいんじゃない?
Isn't tonight fine?
踊ればいいんじゃない?
Isn't it fine to dance?
フラフラ踊れば
If we dance unsteadily
1234 累全 愚言 厳選 温泉
1234 Accumulation, foolish words, selection, spa
ラスバン ダンガンダン サンサラ
Last ban, dangandan, sansara
何してんだ
What are you doing?
高まった感動の再会
A heightening emotional reunion
集まった愛情の Wi-Fi
Gathered affection's Wi-Fi
持ち寄って上等の 以外 いらしてよ
Bring it together, other than superior, please come
重なって
...overlapping
今だに緩い状態 集みとパイ満ちたいだね
Still in a loose state, I want to fill up on pi
バイバイバイバイ
Bye bye bye bye
愛包 愛包で ほれほれよ とろけ出そうね 甘いスパイ レモン 期待したいね いっぱい満杯
Ai-pau, Ai-pau, look look, melting, sweet spy lemon, I want to expect it, full to the brim
乾杯 合成に ほれほれよ ミルキーみたいね
Cheers, synthesis, look look, it's like milky
愛よろい 集まんなか バイバババイババイ
Love armor, gathering, bye bababai babai
賑やかな脳内 脳裏の煩悩愛バイ
Lively brain, the worldly desires love in the mind
可愛いお耳を咲かせて ダンスホールじゃ暇人もヒーロー
Make the cute ears bloom, even idle people are heroes
合切 今夜はボレロ 持ち寄って人類...
Altogether, tonight's a bolero, bringing humanity...
...仲良くやって笑わす
...getting along and making people laugh
お代わり美味しいでしょう
A refill is delicious, isn't it?
全人類降臨 舞踏会の迷宮 徹底的に一日中 エンジン全開で倍になるような
All humanity descends, the labyrinth of the ball, all day long, engines full throttle, doubling
脳みそもとろとろのような
Like your brain is melting too
次元をスローガンに踊りまして 煩悩創砕
Dancing with dimensions as slogan, crushing desires
突きまして低音を操作 バイバババイババイ
And then, controlling the bass, bye bababai babai
人類最高のダンスタイム
Humanity's greatest dance time
愛包ダンスホール
Ai-pau Dancehall
Aipaku Dance Hall
愛包ダンスホール
僕らが生まれて初めて知る音は
The first sound we know when we are born
心臓の鼓動だ
is the sound of our heartbeat.
どたどたどたどたどたてんてたどた
Thump-thump-thump-thump...
それはリズムと知った
We knew that was rhythm.
古も今時も
In the past and in the present,
サイビートが僕たちを紡いで繋いでんだろう
Cybeat must be spinning and connecting us together.
タタタタタハイ
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-Hi!
愛配愛配でオレオレ　トロケチャウネ
With Aipai Aipai, Ole Ole, melting away...
甘ズッパイデモンQアイ
Sweet and sour...
乾杯完全にホレホレ
Cheers, completely infatuated...
ヨンミラミミミタイアイホドリアクマネッカパパラパッパ
Dancing infatuated...
ラガララララガラララ
La-ga-la-la-la...
まるでダンスホールを踊ってるみたい
It's like we're dancing in a dance hall,
生まれ変わったような気分でして
feeling like we've been reborn.
乾杯な今日はボレロ
A toast, today is a bolero.
おすまし顔に反してバカなんて笑って
Laughing about how silly it is, despite the serious look.
テレテッテッテッテッテッテン
Te-re-te-te...
寂しいよな　終わりを近づけるとさ
It's lonely when the end draws near.
終わらないパイのように続けたい
I want it to continue like the endless Pi.
計算なんてできないが
I can't do the math,
おー
Oh...
愛配愛配ダンスホール
Aipai Aipai Dance Hall,
今日はボレロ　トロケチャウネ　甘ズッパイデモンQアイ
today's a bolero... melting away... sweet and sour...
また食べに来てね
Please come to eat again.
あなたならいつでもいいよ
Anytime is fine for you.
おかわり欲しいでしょ
You want seconds, don't you?
愛包ダンスホール
Aipaku Dance Hall
おかわりならもし
If you want seconds...
愛包ダンスホール
Aipaku Dance Hall
どうぞ
Please.
さよならプリンセス　夢に待っている
Goodbye, Princess, waiting in a dream.
眠り沈むその姿は華やかな
Your form sinking into sleep is brilliant.
魅惑のハッピーエンド　私とさよならだ
A captivating happy ending, it's goodbye to me.
さよならプリンセス
Sayonara Princess
鏡の中一人縛られて
Tied up alone in the mirror,
頭の中に駆け回る毎日です
it's a daily cycle running through my head.
ずっと　ずっと　だって私変わらないし
Forever and ever, because I don't change.
夢もないし　口もないし
I have no dreams, no mouth,
つまらないし　可愛くもないし
it's boring, and I'm not even cute.
分からないし　仕方ないし
I don't understand, it can't be helped.
不意に気づいたらまるで
Before I knew it, it's like...
指を解く火花になっていたんだ
it had become a spark that unbinds the fingers.
壊れた大人の愛嬌なんだ
It's the charm of a broken adult.
期待を懸けた私のことなんて気にしないでね
Please don't worry about me, whom you put your expectations on.
さよならプリンセス　夢に待っている
Goodbye, Princess, waiting in a dream.
一人浮かぶその姿は華やかな
That form floating alone is brilliant.
魅惑のハッピーエンド　私とさよならだ
A captivating happy ending, it's goodbye to me.
間抜けたプリンセス　過去とバイバイだ
A foolish princess, it's bye-bye to the past.
この際ね何も全てを燃やしてしまおう
At this point, let's just burn everything.
このまま宙を泳いであの星になれたら
If I could just swim through space and become that star...
私　私とさよならだ
I... it's goodbye to me.
埃まみれ　妬み渦巻いた
Dust-covered, swirling with jealousy,
体の中から絡まる毎日です
it's a daily tangle from within my body.
ずっと　ずっと　だってあなた騙しやすいし　変わらないし
Forever and ever, because you're easy to deceive, and you don't change.
脚長いし　面白いし
Your legs are long, you're interesting,
顔も可愛いし
and your face is cute too.
さりげないし　仕方ないし
You're nonchalant, it can't be helped.
溢れるオーラはまるで
The overflowing aura is like...
キラキラ輝く王座みたいね
a sparkling, shining throne, isn't it?
めろめろ私も目配くないね
I'm head over heels, I can't look away.
古き昨日の私のことなんて流さないでね
Please don't wash away the me from the old yesterday.
さよならプリンセス　愛に酔っている
Goodbye, Princess, drunk on love.
一人浮かぶその姿は鮮やかな
That form floating alone is vivid.
理想のハッピーエンド　私とさよならだ
An ideal happy ending, it's goodbye to me.
さよならプリンセス　全てバイバイだ
Goodbye, Princess, it's bye-bye to everything.
巡り巡る幸せに絡まるほど
As much as it's entangled in the repeating happiness...
間抜けなハッピーエンド　可愛くなれたかな
A foolish happy ending, did I become cute?
私　私は既に分かっていたんだ
I... I already knew.
花よさよならか
Are the flowers saying goodbye?
Mr. Showtime
ちょっとどうもこうも言い切れない
I can't quite say one way or the other.
散らかっちゃってまとまらない
It's all cluttered and won't come together.
独りぼっちの世界に響くモノローグ
A monologue echoing in a lonely world.
あれもこれも出来やしない
I can't do this or that.
ぐるぐる回るメリーゴーランド
A merry-go-round spinning round and round.
踊って踊っていくほどお手のものハグリ
The more I dance and dance, the more I'm in my element...
あっちこっちすんで踏ん張って
Staying here and there and holding on.
誇り高き演目の行き止まりでも
Even at the dead end of a proud performance,
諦めない　駆けるスターダム
I won't give up, racing towards stardom.
なら一人ぼっちじゃつまらないでしょ
Then being all alone is boring, isn't it?
青砂の迷い子も全てあの星を目指せ
Even the lost children in the blue sand, aim for that star.
まるで掴めやしない　届きやしない願いの島まで
To the island of wishes that can't be grasped, can't be reached...
明日へ
Towards tomorrow.
銀河を駆けゆく
Running across the galaxy
旅人たちを乗せて
Carrying the travelers
恐れはしない
I won't be afraid
憂いもしない
I won't grieve
呆れるほどに
To an amazing degree
無謀な愉快な冒険さ
It's a recklessly delightful adventure
止まらないまま It's Showtime!
Without stopping, it's showtime!
待って待って
Wait, wait
おかしいな
Something's wrong
次の台詞が
The next line...
ど忘れ
...I completely forgot
迷子になった世界に降りる
Descending into a world where I'm lost
遠慮なく
Without hesitation
悩んで
Worrying
どうしてやるせない？
Why is it so helpless?
不和の音を
The sound of discord
小指へ結いて
Tie it to your pinky finger
真っ暗夢想も苦くてたまらない
Pitch black daydreams are unbearably bitter
最高でワンダー！
The best and wonderful!
悩んで遠回り
Worrying and taking a detour
空回り
Spinning my wheels
おいでよ 罠
Come on, a trap
底底こそが
The very bottom
最高のショウタイム
Is the best showtime
なら聴き及んで仕舞いましょう
So let's listen until the end
呆気ないだろう？
Isn't it underwhelming?
エンジン全開 絶好調
Engine at full throttle, in peak condition
スカしたママ またにもデザート
Acting cool, once more, a dessert
恐れはしない
I won't be afraid
救えもしない
I can't even save it
不完全燃焼
Incomplete combustion
花火になってまた飛ばそうぜ チャレンジャー
Become a firework and fly again, Challenger
暗い空も 涙も 吹き飛ばすように
To blow away the dark sky and tears
払えよ
Sweep it away
痛いよ
It hurts
鳴らして醒めてね
Make a sound and wake up
顔上げて ショウはここから
Look up, the show starts from here
凡才の凡庸な
An ordinary person's mediocre
方法の提示を
Presentation of methods
増したました ナルシスト
A narcissist, more and more
決まれ決まれ 一等賞
Win, win the first prize
噛ませ ハッタリもちょっと
Give it a go, a little bluffing
真骨頂
My true worth
見切り発車
A snap judgment
バーナブル・ショウ
A burnable show
表も焼き切り
Burning the surface
お目玉喰らっても
Even if I get scolded
スキル・ワンダー
Skill wonder
止められやしない
Nothing can stop me
語り尽くせない思い出星を
Memories like stars that can't be fully told
詰め込んだ風船
A balloon filled with them
銀河を駆けてゆく 旅人たちを乗せて
Across the galaxy, carrying the travelers
まだ終わらない
It's not over yet
終わりたくない
I don't want it to end
それでもいつかは
But even so, someday...
その日が来るまで
...until that day comes
いざ躍り明かせ 歌い明かせ
Now, dance all night, sing all night
スターダスト・パレード
Stardust Parade
果てない物語
A story that never ends
演じ踊り
Performing and dancing
忘れはしない
I won't forget
嘆きはしない
I won't grieve
サヨナラじゃないから
Because it's not goodbye
無謀な愉快な伝説は
An adventurous and delightful legend
発展途上さ
Is still in the making
Step by Step
破茶滅茶なワンダーを
A chaotic wonder
綴るのさ
Writing it down
Mr. Showtime!
あー、歌ったぞー！
Ah, we sang it!
楽しかったねー
That was fun.
楽しかったー！
It was fun!
みんな来てくれたの？ありがとう！
Did everyone come for me? Thank you!
いえいえー
No problem.
あーにゃーちゃん！
Anya-chan!
お誕生日おめでとう〜！！
Happy Birthday!!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとなんだけどさ…
I'm grateful, but...
ありがとなんだけどさ、どういうテンションなの、これ？
I'm grateful, but what's with this energy?
フレア何やってんのさ、こういうテンションだっけ？
Flare, what are you doing? Was the energy like this?
そうだよ、お祝いテンション
That's right, it's celebration energy.
あ、そうなの？逆にどんなんだと思ってたの？
Oh, really? What did you think it was?
お祝いテンションなんなの？
What is celebration energy?
そうだよ、そうなの。
Exactly, that's it.
そうなんだ。
I see.
アーニャちゃんは…
Anya-chan...
うん。
Yeah.
何歳になったの？
How old have you turned?
私は、2才になったの！
I turned 2 years old!
みたい。
Apparently.
みたいなの。
Something like that.
そうだよ。
Indeed.
アイリスは、何歳なの？
IRyS, how old are you?
え、アイリスは…
Eh, IRyS is...
ちょっとまだ言ってないでしょ！
Wait, I haven't said it yet!
まだ、まだ言ってないから！
I haven't said it yet!
聞いてないから！
I'm not listening!
何歳、アイリスは何歳なの？
How old, how old is IRyS?
アイリスは…
IRyS is...
8歳なの！
I'm 8 years old!
8歳なんだー
8 years old, huh?
あ、おめでとう！
Ah, congrats!
ありがとうな！
Thanks!
ありがとう、アイリスもありがとな。
Thank you, and thank you IRyS too.
アイリスもありがとな、おめでとう。
IRyS too, thank you. Congrats.
頑張った頑張った。
Good job, good job.
もうやめて、もう…
Stop it already...
あー、どういうテンション…
Ah, what is this energy...
私はもう消えます。
I'm going to disappear now.
アーニャ！逃がさないよ！
Anya! I won't let you escape!
うわぁ〜！恥ずかしいんだけど！
Uwah~! This is so embarrassing!
なぁ、ということでね。
Well, so.
ね、Mr. Showtime、4人で歌ったんですけれども。
We just sang 'Mr. Showtime' with the four of us.
いかがでしたでしょうか、感想とか、曲の感想とか。
How was it? Any thoughts on the performance or the song?
もう、めっちゃ難しかったんだわ！
It was seriously so difficult!
高いところと低いところでボボボボボボって
With the high parts and low parts going bo-bo-bo-bo...
ああ、確かにね
Ah, that's true.
低いところばっかだったよ私
I was doing nothing but the low parts.
ありましたね。でもすごかった、かっこよかったですよ。ゴロゴロ〜とかも
You were. But it was amazing, you sounded so cool. Even the growling parts.
本当？イケボアイリス出したことないよって
Really? I've never really done 'cool-voice IRyS' before.
イケボアイリス珍しいからさ、たまにはいいんじゃないかな
Cool-voice IRyS is rare, so I think it's good once in a while.
ま、確かにね。こういうイケボアイリス、レアなんでね
Well, true. This kind of cool-voice IRyS is a rarity.
8歳だもんね
Since you're 8 years old.
8歳なのにね
Even though I'm 8.
もう、もうね、それはそれとして。みんな受け取ってね
Geez, anyway, that aside. Everyone, please take it in...
アイリスのかっこよさを
...IRyS's coolness.
8歳... 8歳... ごめんなさい
8 years old... 8 years old... I'm sorry.
絶対この後アーカイブ見返して
You absolutely have to watch the archive again after this.
やだやだ、見たくない
No, no, I don't want to see it!
見返してほしい。回すたびに今度は見よ
I want you to rewatch it. Watch it every time it loops.
でもアーニャのライブはちゃんと見てね。この部分だけ飛ばして
But make sure you watch Anya's live properly. Just skip this part.
一番大事なとこでしょ
That's the most important part!
めっちゃ喉乾いてんな
Man, my throat is so dry.
あら？喉乾いてきた？
Oh? Are you getting thirsty?
急に喉乾いてきたわ。このテンションで喉乾いたわ
Suddenly my throat is parched. This excitement made me thirsty.
なら乾いた。あ、アーニャお腹空いた... あ、お飲み物ないかな？
Then I'm dry. Ah, Anya is hungry... Ah, is there anything to drink?
あ、なんか来た、なんか来た
Oh, something's coming, something's coming.
アーニャちゃん！たくさん歌って喉乾いたでしょ？
Anya-chan! You've been singing a lot, so you must be thirsty, right?
そうだよ
That's right.
これ飲んでほしいのら
I want you to drink this, nanora.
何その声？
What's with that voice?
こぼしてる、こぼしてる。なんか熱そうなの出てきた
She's spilling it, she's spilling it. Something hot-looking came out.
はい、これは
Here, this is...
何これ？怪しいな。熱っ！これ何？
What is this? Suspicious. Hot! What is this?
ねえ、湯気立ってる。熱っ、熱っ
Hey, it's steaming. Hot, hot!
熱そうだよ、本当
It really looks hot.
うんとこどっこいしょ熱いもの。飲んで、飲んで
Heave-ho, something really hot. Drink it, drink it.
まあ一旦飲むか。飲んで飲んで
Well, I guess I'll try it. Drink up, drink up.
本当に飲んだ！本当に飲んだ！
She actually drank it! She actually drank it!
美味しい？美味しい？
Is it good? Is it good?
ふぅ... めっちゃ、めっちゃ美味しかったよ。でも
Phew... It was really, really delicious. But...
本当？怪しかったけどさ、めっちゃ美味しかった？
Really? It was suspicious, but it was really delicious?
よかった... 美味しかったならよかった
Good... I'm glad if it was tasty.
うわー！え、何、何？
Whoa! Eh, what, what?!
え、どういうこと？デカくなった？
Wait, what's happening? Did I get big?!
アーニャ！どういうこと？
Anya! What's going on?!
デカっ！あんまり動き回らないでよ
She's huge! Don't move around too much!
デカくなっちゃった！ねえ、すごい揺れるね。これ潰れるかな？
I've become huge! Hey, it's shaking like crazy. Is this gonna collapse?
みんな潰れるじゃん。ガミガミやめてよ
We're all gonna get crushed! Stop nagging me!
あ！アイリス！
Ah! IRyS!
ああー！！
AAAAAAHH!!
残りはルーナ先輩、元に戻してくださいよ。じゃないと、潰しちゃうぞ
Luna-senpai, turn me back to normal. Or else I'll crush you!
潰しちゃうぞー
I'll crush you~!
ねえ、もしかしてお茶かければ元に戻るの？
Hey, maybe if I pour tea on myself, I'll turn back?
暴力、暴力はやめて！
Violence! Stop the violence!
それだ、やってよルーナ！
That's it! Do it, Luna!
やっちゃうよ。頼む、もう一回かけてみる。足元に。普通にかけるのら
I'll do it! Please, I'll try pouring it one more time. On her feet. Just regular pouring, nanora.
戻れるかな？あ、戻った！え？
Can she return? Oh, she's back! Eh?
さっきはよくもやってくれたな
You really put me through it earlier.
ルーナ先輩、ルーナ先輩、どういう飲み物なんですかそれ？
Luna-senpai, Luna-senpai, what kind of drink is that exactly?
小さくなったならね
Well, now she's gotten tiny.
そんなことはどうだっていいんだよ。なんなん、さっきはよくも踏みつけてやってくれたね
Never mind that! What the heck, you had the nerve to trample on me earlier!
アーニャ、アーニャちゃん、ちっちゃくて可愛いね。餌あげたいよ。餌あげたくなっちゃった
Anya, Anya-chan, you're so small and cute! I want to feed you. I feel like giving you a treat.
酷いことしないで。可愛いから、ご褒美あげちゃう
Don't do anything mean! Since you're so cute, I'll give you a reward.
え、どういうご褒美？
Eh? What kind of reward?
アーニャちゃん、おっと、それは... それは... アイリスの足が！
Anya-chan, oops, that's... that's... IRyS's leg!
パンチラと見せかけてパンチ！
A punch disguised as a panty shot!
待って、なんて残酷な。痛い、痛い。ちょっと2歳児にやることじゃないよ
Wait, how cruel! Ouch, ouch! Hey, that's not something you do to a 2-year-old!
2歳児だと思います？2歳児、2歳児だよ、こんなにちっちゃくて。可愛いね
You think she's a 2-year-old? A 2-year-old, she really is a 2-year-old, being this tiny. So cute.
アーニャにさ、プレゼントもあげたことだし、そろそろ帰ろっか
Well, we've given Anya her present, so it's about time we headed home.
帰るのね。時間だし、じゃあね
Heading home then. It's time, so see ya!
待って、その前に元に戻してくださいよ。ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って！
Wait, turn me back before you go! Wait a second! Wait a second!!
Here we go, thank you! The party's over.
お芝居はおしまい
The play is over.
止まらない weekend, weekend
Unstoppable weekend, weekend.
Always be in the show, the show time
Wow! Get up, get ready!
新しい今も back up してくれないように
So that even the new 'now' won't hold us back.
ぐるぐる回る 必ず追いついて見せるから
Spinning round and round, I'll definitely show you I can catch up.
遠く今待って 正しいことは与えられてた
Wait far away now, the right things were given to us.
送り足を送れたのは君だけ
The only one who could send me off was you.
愛していたい二人じゃなきゃ始まらない
I want to keep loving you, it won't start unless it's the two of us.
歪なステップでもいい 今は君と踊っていたい
Distorted steps are fine, I just want to dance with you right now.
ただ生きるためのまじないをそこに残した
I left a charm there just for the sake of living.
命を負ってほしい君と短く長い季節を辿って
I want you to bear this life, as we trace through short and long seasons together.
ないないまで はじめまして あら
Until nothing is left, nice to meet you. Oh?
…だろ
...right?
でもどうしても引き剥がして
But I must tear it away
その深い深い瞳に別の色を乗せたい
I want to put a different color in those deep, deep eyes
置いてきた空振りを今蹴り飛ばして
Kicking away the swings and misses I left behind
駆けつけるから
Because I'm coming for you
甘く淫らに見せるから
Because I'll show you something sweet and lewd
バイバイしても元通りでもない
Even if we say goodbye, it won't be like it was
私に成せることはないが
There's nothing I can do, but...
でもそうだきっと今更と言って
But that's right, surely you'll say it's too late
仰ぐ
Looking up
頷き広がる空から
From the nodding, spreading sky
愛していたい　うっかりしなきゃ始まらない
I want to love; it won't start unless I'm careless
いびつなステップでも今は君と踊っていたい
Even with distorted steps, I want to dance with you now
ただ生きるためのまじないをそこに残した
I left a spell there just for living
命を追って欲しい君と短くない季節渡って
I want you to chase life, crossing seasons with you that aren't short
バイバイしても元通りでもない
Even if we say goodbye, it won't be like it was
私にできることはあるか
Is there anything I can do?
このテンポそうだこんな歌ならどうだ
This tempo, yes, how about a song like this?
だらしなくないけどちょっといいかもね
It's not slovenly, but it might be a bit good
もっと響かせて
Make it resonate more
この道に駆けて
Running on this path
ずうっといっしょ！
Together Forever!
10年越しても窓の外のせいで手摺り減った
Even after 10 years, the handrail wore down because of the outside window
10年見逃して窓の外見せる変えるなくなった
Overlooking it for 10 years, there's no more showing or changing the outside window
繋ごうよ手と手を背中も引き込んで
Let's join hands, drawing our backs in too
お互いに足を引っ張ったお互いに充電した想い出がずうっといっしょ
Pulling each other's legs, recharging each other, memories are always together
3回目の夏誰からも見られていない気がしたんだ
The third summer, I felt like no one was watching me
千々に砕けて昼の街期待しないようにしたんだ
Shattered into pieces, I tried not to expect anything from the city during the day
そうやってもう白黒のストイベ自棄になった
Doing that, the black and white event made me desperate
あたし面死にたくて仕方ないこんな顔台無しにしたいと思えないもん
I can't help wanting to die, I can't imagine wanting to ruin this face
供に過ごした日々が
The days we spent together
鮮やかな幸せが代えの利かないドラマになってたらいいな
I hope the vivid happiness becomes an irreplaceable drama
離れ離れなんて誰かが継ぎ接いだバグだよね
Being apart is just a bug someone patched together, right?
あなたの一生の後悔として添い遂げるよ
I'll live out my life as your lifelong regret
大切なものってなに？今失くしたそれ
What is the most precious thing? The thing you just lost
あたしと間違いを犯したな取り返しがつかないです
You made a mistake with me; it's irreversible
恋焦がれる時も止める時も腐れ縁の中でずうっといっしょ
When longing, when stopping, in this inseparable bond, always together
もうちょっと普通に悲しいこと悲しいと思いたかった
I wanted to feel sad things as sad, just a bit more normally
叙情の端に感情隠して楽になりたかった
I wanted to hide my emotions at the edge of lyricism and be at ease
精一杯懸命に生きてくださいね
Please live your life as hard as you can
あたし面死にたくて仕方ないあの子の言いなりになんていたくないの
I can't help wanting to die, I don't want to be at that girl's beck and call
あなただけひとりで
Just you alone
あたしの目を盗んで幸せになろうなんて思わないで
Don't think about becoming happy behind my back
髪を乾かしてくれた夜から
Since the night you dried my hair
あたしは壊されてんだよ
I've been broken
あなたの一生の後悔として添い遂げるよ
I'll live out my life as your lifelong regret
外れなくなってしまった指輪みたいに
Like a ring that won't come off
今もずっと欲しがっている最低でいてよ
I'm still wanting it; please be the worst
一緒にいた時の方が私可愛かったな
I was cuter when we were together
あなたの一生の後悔として添い遂げるよ
I'll live out my life as your lifelong regret
大切なものってなに？胸打したそれ
What is the most precious thing? That which struck your heart
あたしと間違いを犯したな取り返しがつかないです
You made a mistake with me; it's irreversible
恋焦がれる時も止める時もどん底で眠っていても遅くないわ　墓までずうっといっしょ
When longing, when stopping, even if sleeping at rock bottom, it's not too late. All the way to the grave, always together
ずっといっしょ！
Always together!
廃棄に寄ったケイデンス
A cadence leaning towards disposal
もう嫌なこと全部投げ出しちゃって
Throwing away everything unpleasant
白に御同座　正義へ
Joining the white, towards justice
超あられもない話は止まらないよ
Incredibly immodest stories won't stop
惰性で待った成々へ
Towards the results waited for through inertia
生まれ育ち　内側が悪かったせいで
Because my inner upbringing was bad
全部あなたのせいで
Everything is your fault
今日傘を持ってくるのも忘れてた
I also forgot to bring an umbrella today
興味ないそんなトピック
No interest in such a topic
むかつく陽性に最後はありがとう　執着に愛を
Thanks to the annoying positivity in the end, love to the obsession
ヘルメット姿　祝ったような
A helmet-clad figure, as if celebrating
サウンドがスリンカー　歌ってみたシャドー
The sound is 'Slinker', a cover-video shadow
黎明の夜明けまで待てよ
Wait until the break of dawn
歓喜をもっと求めえ
Seek more joy
もう嫌なこと全部投げ出したいね
I want to throw away everything unpleasant
愛想を同座　正義へ
Affability joining the same seat, towards justice
今日さ傘を持ってくるのを忘れてた
Today, you see, I forgot to bring an umbrella
代えがたい冒険みたいな
Like an irreplaceable adventure
つまらなくなった戦争
A war that has become boring
結局波が怖いの
After all, I'm afraid of the waves
液晶にずっと療養しなんだ
I wasn't convalescing in the LCD for long
どんな未来を総称に選んで
Choosing what kind of future as a general term
誰が生贄になるのかな
I wonder who will become the sacrifice
踊る鳥は不審
Dancing birds are suspicious
こうべ垂れて来い
Come with your head bowed
会食もなく垂れ流しの御多幸と寄り添い長年見たり
Watching for years, nestling with constant outflow of happiness without a banquet
街明けた海
The sea where dawn broke
穿たれた不運
The pierced misfortune
汚れなき至上の最禍の歴史に戻ろ目覚ました星は輝く皇光
Return to the history of the pure, supreme recurring calamity, the awakened star shines with brilliant light
ドクター気取りです
Acting like a doctor
愛、爆破テロ
Love, bombing terrorism
簡単になれば
If it becomes simple
埋めた、目溜めた、埋めた
Buried, eyes collected, buried
ドクター気取りです
Acting like a doctor
愛想、良いかも
Affability might be good
窓、開けても
Even if the window is open
埋めた、目溜めた、埋めた
Buried, eyes collected, buried
何処にもない体得いたら
If there's an attainment found nowhere else
壊れて泣いてる夢を見たんだよ
I had a dream of breaking and crying
直系には嘘耳やってくる
False ears come to the direct line
顔が溶けだれちゃうよ
My face is going to melt away
見せかけ権利を盗ったんだ
I stole make-believe rights
忘れて欲しいものや
Things I want to forget and such
どうやら生き延びてしまった　生き延びてしまったんだ
Apparently I've survived, I've ended up surviving
足が地に着かないよ
My feet don't touch the ground
嘘が溶けだしたんだ
The lies have started to melt
嘘、撫ぜて欲しい本能は
The instinct to want lies caressed
どうやら干したと思った　干したと思ったんだ
Apparently I thought I'd dried out, I thought I'd dried out
口上
Prologue
ドクター気取りです
Acting like a doctor
本番やめるよ
I'm stopping the real performance
卑力、感度モニター、雲泥、独尊、特権、特権、法だけ
Low power, sensitivity monitor, world of difference, arrogance, privilege, privilege, only the law
回した　回した　回した
Was turned, turned, turned
顔が溶けだれちゃうよ
My face is going to melt away
見せかけ権利を盗ったんだ
I stole make-believe rights
なくなって欲しいものや
Things I want to disappear and such
どうやら生き延びてしまった　生き延びてしまったんだ
Apparently I've survived, I've ended up surviving
おどけ、ドクターになってしまう
Ending up as a jesting doctor
人が居座りに集まる
People gather to stay
嘘、承知お見舞いします
Knowing it's a lie, I'll pay you a visit
震えてない 震えてない 震えてないみたい
I'm not shaking, not shaking, not shaking at all
震えてないみたい Make up ちゃんと
I'm not shaking at all, I'll do my makeup properly
Hah! Oh my god!
That was so much fun!
I sang so many songs!
ねー、いっぱい歌っちゃったね。
Man, I really sang a lot.
ゲストのみなさんたちともね、歌っちゃいましたけれども。
I sang with all the guests too.
みんなお気に入りとかある？どうだった？
Does everyone have a favorite? How was it?
How was it?
How was all the—how were all the performances?
If you guys have any favorite, don't forget to post with the hashtag by the way,
#CuriousTune3D!
Tell me your favorite, or like, you know, memorable moments from the 3D birthday live.
Yippee!
Oh my goodness! Now it's announcement time!
Ada ads ya guys, no skipping ads ya guys by the way.
There are ads, guys, so no skipping ads, guys, by the way.
Habis ini akan ada ads, jadi no skipping-skipping ya. Okay?
There'll be ads after this, so no skipping, okay?
Don't skip the ads, okay?
Oh my god! The first one is...
Anya Melfissa Birthday Celebration 2025
Oh my god!
誕生日記念 2025年のグッズだってー！
It's the 2025 birthday commemorative merch!
The first one is... this beautiful, you know, this beautiful birthday merchandise.
Yes, that's right! We will be having 2025 merchandise, Anya Melfissa merchandise. Yippee!
Ada birthday 2025 merchandise, guys. Yippee!
There's 2025 birthday merch, guys. Yippee!
Ini art-nya, art-nya gila keren banget nggak sih, guys? Oh my god!
The art, the art is crazy cool, isn't it guys? Oh my god!
ねー、イラストめっちゃすごくない？ねー。
Right? Isn't the illustration amazing? Right?
こちらの素敵なグッズのキービジュアルはね、SOLANI先生が担当してくださいました。
This lovely merch's key visual was done by SOLANI-sensei.
すごく素敵なイラストで、私もお気に入りです。
It's a really wonderful illustration, and it's one of my favorites.
Aku suka banget sama illustration kali ini, gila keren banget, Anya banget nggak sih? Hmm.
I really love this illustration, it's so cool and so very "Anya", isn't it? Hmm.
ってことでね、Let's take a look at each item one by one, shall we?
So, let's take a look at each item one by one, shall we?
Let's look at them!
The first one is this...
Rubber Mat
Rubber mat! Rubber mat with the key visual.
Rubber mat pakai key visual yang tadi ya guys. Yes, keren banget, oh my god!
A rubber mat using the key visual from before, guys. Yes, it's so cool, oh my god!
Keren banget, oh my god!
It's so cool, oh my god!
ねー、キービジュアルがプリントされたラバーマットです。
Right, it's a rubber mat printed with the key visual.
Ini bisa dipakai buat meja-meja nggak apa-apa, buat main apa ya?
You can use this for your desk, or for playing... what was it?
Buat main board game gitu juga nggak apa-apa.
For playing board games and such, that's fine too.
Terus buat main catur juga nggak apa-apa, dibuat tidur juga nggak apa-apa, guys.
Then for playing chess is fine, even using it for sleeping is fine, guys.
Ya terserah ya guys, dibuat tidur juga nggak apa-apa.
Well, it's up to you guys, it's okay even for sleeping.
Yeah, you can use this rubber mat anywhere you like, basically. Hmm.
And then, the next one...
The next merchandise...
Acrylic diorama stand! アクリルジオラマスタンドです。
Acrylic diorama stand! It's an acrylic diorama stand.
This isn't your usual acrylic stand, by the way.
It's made with three layers for a more dynamic, three-dimensional look, guys. Oh my goodness!
Ini bukan acrylic stand biasa, guys, ada tiga lapis yang bikin tampilannya kelihatan lebih hidup.
This isn't just a regular acrylic stand, guys, it has three layers that make it look more alive.
Kayak... kayak aku kan keris hidup ya guys. Cocok banget nggak sih?
Like... like how I'm a living kris, right guys? Doesn't it fit perfectly?
The illustration comes with a design frame, so it's perfect for display.
ねー、イラストにデザインフレームがついた、ディスプレイにぴったりの逸品です。
Right, it's a piece with a design frame on the illustration, perfect for display.
Cocok banget buat display pokoknya, guys.
It's just perfect for display, guys.
You can place it on your desk next to the rubber mat as well.
Taruh di meja kalian sama rubber mat yang tadi juga bisa.
You can also put it on your desk along with that rubber mat.
Terus, ya, dibuat—dimakan juga bisa, guys.
Then, well, you could even... eat it, guys.
Dimakan juga sebenarnya bisa, aduh... aduh ya...
You actually could eat it too... Oh boy...
Biasalah ya guys, adrenalin dari habis live, jadi ngomongnya aneh-aneh.
It's normal guys, the adrenaline from finishing a live, so I'm saying weird things.
Okay, the next merchandise... Shall we take a look at the next merchandise?
So cute! Look at this! It's an acrylic keychain...
...of general outfit Anya.
通常衣装のアクリルキーホルダーです。めっちゃ可愛くない？
It's an acrylic keychain of my regular outfit. Isn't it super cute?
Yeah, me in my regular outfit. So cute. Mini Anya.
You can take it anywhere, guys. Oh my god! On your bag...
Di tas juga bisa. Terus di apa lagi ya? Di dompet juga bisa.
You can put it on your bag. And where else? On your wallet too.
...di tas juga bisa.
...on your bag too.
Di dompet juga bisa.
On your wallet too.
Terserah deh di mana aja, guys.
Wherever you want, guys.
ねえ、お出かけとかにぜひ使ってください！
Please use it when you go out!
ということで、次はこちらです！
So, next is this!
こちらです！可愛い...
It's this! Cute...
...可愛くない？
...Isn't it cute?
可愛いとカッコいいが...
Cute and cool are...
...混ざり合ってる...
...mixed together...
...ハンドミラーです！
...hand mirror!
The design of the mirror has a chic design...
...perfect for using at home or taking it with you when you're out.
It's both stylish and really easy to use.
Inikanya gila stylish banget guys.
This one looks incredibly stylish, guys.
Terus ada kayak motif-motif Anya gitu...
And there's Anya-themed motifs...
...di belakangnya kayak gini nih, guys.
...on the back like this, guys.
Keren banget nggak sih? Oh my god.
Isn't it so cool? Oh my god.
Ini perfect banget kalau kalian mau keluar...
This is perfect if you want to go out...
...terus ya biasanya...
...and usually...
...untuk yang butuh kaca lah guys.
...for those who need a mirror, guys.
Daripada pakai HP mending pakai...
Instead of using your phone, better use...
...hand mirror-nya Anya Melfissa. Iya nggak sih?
...Anya Melfissa's hand mirror. Right?
シックなデザインのハンドミラーなので...
Since it's a chicly designed hand mirror...
...家で使っても良し、お外で使っても良しの...
...it's good for home use or outside use...
...使いやすいミラーとなっております。
...making it an easy-to-use mirror.
Di rumah juga boleh, guys.
At home is fine too, guys.
Di rumah, di luar, terserah kalian, okay?
At home, outside, it's up to you, okay?
Next up! Next up is this!
VOICE PACK! Oh my god!
Yes, Voice Pack! And this time...
...the script is written by yours truly, Anya Melfissa.
Just like pretty much every year.
Every year I, I write my own birthday Voice Pack.
ね、こちらね、台本、また今年もね...
The script, once again this year...
...また、えー、アーニャ・メルフィッサです。
...is by Anya Melfissa.
台本担当アーニャ・メルフィッサです。よろしくお願いします。
I'm the scriptwriter, Anya Melfissa. Please look forward to it.
毎年しながらの、はい。
Doing it every year, yes.
And of course, there are also special bonuses...
...you get for buying the merchandise set!
Hmm, here are the bonuses.
Postcard with a duplicate autograph!
Yeah, duplicate autograph means...
...the autograph is, you know, foil-stamped.
Tanda tangannya jadi kayak dicetak pakai foil stamping ya, guys.
The autograph is like it's printed using foil stamping, guys.
And don't worry, it's not a limited edition this time.
So everyone can get one!
Bukan limited edition, guys. Jadi oh my god, beli sih!
It's not limited edition, guys. So oh my god, buy it!
Udah nggak limited, masa nggak beli? Iya nggak?
It's not limited anymore, so why not buy it? Right?
Udah dibuat nggak limited, masa nggak beli, guys?
Since it's not limited, how could you not buy it, guys?
Gila, keterlaluan banget sih.
Seriously, that's just too much.
Keterlaluan banget.
That's really too much.
And then the next bonus...
The next bonus is...
...the Voice Pack...
...the Voice Pack translations! Yes...
...I forgot to mention my Voice Pack is only available in, you know, in Japanese.
So if you guys, you know, get the bonus...
...one of them is actually English and Bahasa Indonesia scripts...
...of my Voice Pack.
Jadi Voice Pack-nya cuma ada Bahasa Jepang.
So the Voice Pack is only in Japanese.
Tapi tenang aja, guys, bonusnya ada...
But don't worry, guys, the bonus includes...
...translation Bahasa Indonesia sama translation Bahasa Inggris juga.
...Indonesian and English translations too.
Jadi tunggu apa lagi?
So what are you waiting for?
Tunggu apa lagi?
What are you waiting for?
こちらのね、ボイスはね、毎年ながら日本語なんですけれども...
This Voice Pack, as always, is in Japanese, but...
...こちらボーナスとして英語と、えー、インドネシア語の台本もつくので...
...as a bonus, English and Indonesian scripts are included, so...
...ぜひ皆さん、楽しんでください。
...everyone, please look forward to it.
いろんな言語でね。
In various languages.
ということで次、こちらです！
So next, it's this!
YAY! Special bonus!
If you buy the merchandise set...
...you'll get a special card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game release...
...last September! Oh my god!
Buat teman-temannya yang beli set complete merchandise kali ini...
For friends who buy the complete merchandise set this time...
...kalian bakal dapat satu kartu yang bisa dipakai di hololive Official Card Game...
...you'll get one card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game...
...yang rilis September tahun lalu, guys!
...that released last September, guys!
ね、今回ね、グッズセットをご購入いただいた方に...
Yes, for those who purchased the merchandise set this time...
...あの、昨年九月に発売されたホロライブ公式カードゲームで使用できるカードが...
...a card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game released last September...
...一枚特典として付きます！
...is included as a bonus!
いや、この特典ね、めっちゃ良くない？
Man, isn't this bonus really good?
みんなTCG好きなんだよね。
Everyone loves TCGs, right?
いや、楽しそうだなってずっと見てるのね、アーニャも。
Yeah, Anya's always been watching thinking it looks fun.
いつか私もやりたいなと思ってます。
I'm thinking I want to try it myself someday.
It's an Oshi-holomem card, by the way.
Yeah, your key card to show...
...of your face.
Kartu ini itu oshi holo-mem-card gitu guys.
This card is like an 'oshi holo-mem' card, guys.
For details about the card and how to play, please check the website.
ね、カードの詳細や遊び方についてはね、
As for the card's details and how to play,
ホームページで確認してくださいね。
please check the official website.
Also the card will be available in Japanese only by the way.
日本語、日本語のみですね、カードの方は。
The card itself is Japanese only.
うん。
Yeah.
This bonus by the way is only valid for purchases
made at Hololive Production Official Shop.
Jadi um, ini bonusnya tuh cuma
So um, this bonus is only for
untuk kalian yang beli di
those of you who buy it at
Hololive Production Official Shop ya guys.
the Hololive Production Official Shop, guys.
And there's a second announcement as well!
We still have announcements! Oh my goodness!
ね、こちらね、あの、次の告知、
So, the next announcement,
次のお知らせなんですけれども。
the next bit of news is...
なんと！
Believe it or not!
オリ曲のMVが出まーす！
An MV for my original song is coming out!
オリ曲のMVがね、なんと、
The original song's MV,
今日のこの後22時でね、あのプレミア公開なので楽しみにしといてください。
will have its premiere today at 10:00 PM, so please look forward to it.
MV ori song MV guys, habis ini jam 8 ya guys.
An original song MV, guys, at 8:00 PM after this.
Jam 8 malam Waktu Indonesia Barat habis ini.
8:00 PM Western Indonesia Time after this.
The MV of my original song will be released at 10:00 PM JST
after this, after this live.
It also be released on various music distribution services from,
It'll also be released on various music services from,
you know, from 12:00 AM your timezone.
you know, from 12:00 AM in your timezone.
So please look forward to it! Yippee!
各種音楽配信サービスにもね、リリースされるので、
It will be released on various music services too,
お楽しみにしといてください。
so please look forward to it.
そしてですね、次が最後の曲になるんですけれども、
And now, the next one will be the last song,
ね、みんな楽しみに、きっと楽しみにしてた
but I'm going to sing that song
あの曲を歌います。
that everyone has surely been waiting for.
The next song is going to be the last song.
Sad, but you guys will love this performance. I'll do my best.
Okay, onto the last song then.
My new original song,
Chronic.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah...
Hey
Walking 'round in reality, I'm so done done
Feel like I'm losing my gravity, my vision
Of you that I see clearly in my mind
I'm so you
My thoughts collide in my mind, I know I really should try
To think, to think on my own but oh
We're tied together it's true, I think I'm becoming you
Don't blink, don't blink, eye eye
They're asking who
Took me so far away, far away
Digitally recreate everything
I I wanna show you why I
Parallel we rise
Love it, chk-chk-boom
Chronic, chronic, chronic, collide till we go atomic
Turn it, turn it, turn it to a different space, different wave
Want it, want it, want it, opposites go supersonic
La la la, love it, love it, love it, dive into the fate we made
Sometimes I think you're here, yeah you're my only one
You make it feel so real, outside it's so surreal
Devastation and creation ooh oah
I'll be your shooting star
A new perspective of life while I just try to survive
I know, I know we're not going down
I guess I can't compromise the in-between of our lives
I know, I know I you
You must be who
Took me so far away, far away
Digitally recreate everything
I I wanna show you why I
Parallel we rise
Love it, chk-chk-boom
Chronic, chronic, chronic, collide till we go atomic
Turn it, turn it, turn it to a different space, different wave
Want it, want it, want it, opposites go supersonic
La la la, love it, love it, love it, dive into the fate we made
Whisper, whisper, whisper, come take me right away
Whisper...
Whisper, whisper
Merging right into you, all mine
Me and my only personal way
Press and hold on to continue
It'll always be you
Tell me you won't go away
Imagining maybe one day
That we'll meet in between
Organic life and blue screens
I do need you
Mirror on the wall says
You'll take me so far
Chronic, collide till we go
Turn it, turn it, turn it
to a different space, different ways
Want it, want it, want it
Opposites go supersonic
Love it, love it, love it
Dive into the fate we made
Whisper...
Come take me right away
Merging right into you, all mine
Whisper...
Me and my only personal way
Press and hold on to continue
It'll always be you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
Through the Curious Tune - Anya Melfissa Birthday Live 2025